A Guide to the Papers Ellen Glasgow, 1880-1963
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- CORRESPONDENCE
  - Henry S. Canby to Ellen Glasgow, 1933 May 8; TLS (Box 13)
  - Marian Canby to Ellen Glasgow, 1936 Apr 22; ALS (Box 13)
  - Frank M. Chapman to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 25; ALS (Box 13)
  - H. W. Chase to Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Jan 30; TLS (Box 13)
  - Annette I. Clark to Ellen Glasgow, 1944 Feb 23; TLS (Box 13)
  - Emily Clarkto Ellen Glasgow, 1936 July 14; ALS (Box 13)
  - Glasgow Clark to Ellen Glasgow, enclosing copy of letter to Cabell [Tutwiler?], 1934 Oct 31; TLS w/encl. (Box 13)
  - Jubillant Mai Clark to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 6; Telegram (Box 13)
  - Clara Classen to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Nov 11; TLS (Box 13)
  - Joseph Collins to Ellen Glasgow, n.d.; TLS w/autograph note (Box 13)
  - Joseph Collins to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Sep 10; ALS (Box 13)
  - Joseph Collins to Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Mar 19; ALS (Box 13)
  - Joseph Collins to Ellen Glasgow, 1933 Jan-Sep; ALS, TLS, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Joseph Collins to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Oct 11; TLS (Box 13)
  - Joseph Collins to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Mar 9; TLS (Box 13)
  - Joseph Collins to Ellen Glasgow, 1945 Feb-Apr; TLS, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Lillian A. Comstock to Ellen Glasgow, 1937 Mar 2; TLS (Box 13)
  - Majorie Glasgow to Ellen Glasgow, 1934 Aug 5; ALS (Box 13)
  - Marjorie Glasgow Congreve to Ellen Glasgow, 1940 Aug 6; ALS (Box 13)
  - Jessie Conrad to Ellen Glasgow, 1923 Dec 17; ALS (Box 13)
  - Jessie Conrad Kozenivusku to Ellen Glasgow, 1924 Feb 14; ALS (Box 13)
  - Joseph Conrad to Mr. Doubleday, 1916 Apr 10; ALS (Box 13)
  - Joseph Conrad to Ellen Glasgow, 1923 Apr 4; ALS (Box 13)
  - Page Cooper to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Aug 16; TLS w/encl. (Box 13)
  - Page Cooperto Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Aug 23; TLS (Box 13)
  - Katherine Cooper to Ellen Glasgow, n.d.; ALS (Box 13)
  - E. M. Crutchfield to Ellen Glasgow, 1916 Jan 12; TLS (Box 13)
  - Miss Bennett from Margaret Dashiell, 1941 July 2; ALS (Box 13)
  - Margaret Dashiell to Ellen Glasgow, 1943 Oct 29; ALS (Box 13)
  - Jeanne Dauban to Ellen Glasgow with minutes of a meeting of the Prix Femine and copy of the letter addressed by the French Comite Femina and transmitted by Mlle Dauban to Mrs. Munroe, 1934 Feb 20; TLS (Box 13)
  - Donald Davidson to Ellen Glasgow, 1936 Nov 3; ALS w/encl. (Box 13)
  - Elaine J. Dean to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Jun 26; ALS (Box 13)
  - Fernand Delatte to Ellen Glasgow, 1933 Feb 3; TL (Box 13)
  - Walter Damrosch to Ellen Glasgow, 1940 May 1; TLS w/encl. (Box 13)
  - Walter Damrosch to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 May 27; TLS (Box 13)
  - Request for and Poem by Ellen Glasgow to Walter Damrosch on his eightieth birthday, 1941 Jul 31; TLS; AMsS (Box 13)
  - Walter Damrosch to Ellen Glasgow, n.d.; NS (Box 13)
  - Whitney Darrow to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Oct 14; TLS (Box 13)
  - Whitney Darrow to Ellen Glasgow, 1936 Feb 18; TLS (Box 13)
  - Margaret Deland to Ellen Glasgow, 1926 Nov 26; ALS (Box 13)
  - F. N. Doubleday to Ellen Glasgow, 1914 Dec 9; ALS (Box 13)
  - F. N. Doubleday to Ellen Glasgow, 1916 Jan 1; NS (Box 13)
  - F. N. Doubleday to Ellen Glasgow, 1916 Jun 29; ALS w/encl. (Box 13)
  - F. N. Doubleday to Ellen Glasgow, 1921 Jul 29; ALS (Box 13)
  - Nelson Doubleday to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Aug 24; Telegram (Box 13)
  - Nelson Doubleday to Ellen Glasgow, 1937 Sep 8; ALS (Box 13)
  - Nelson Doubleday to Ellen Glasgow, 1943 Nov 9; TLS (Box 13)
  - Nelson Doubleday to Ellen Glasgow, 1944 Sep 28; TLS (Box 13)
  - Caroline Duke to Ellen Glasgow, 1939 Sep 1; ALS (Box 13)
  - Lord Duncanon to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Mar 22; ALS w/typescript (Box 13)
  - Paul W. Donham to Ellen Glasgow, 1944 Apr 10; TLS (Box 13)
  - Walter Prichard Eaton to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Nov 15; TLS (Box 13)
  - Maurice Francis Egan to Ellen Glasgow, 1922 Oct 15; ALS (Box 13)
  - Edmund H. Eitel to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Dec 10; ALS (Box 13)
  - C. S. Evans to Ellen Glasgow, 1928 Dec 21; TLS (Box 13)
  - C. S. Evans to Ellen Glasgoww/encl., 1930 Feb 19; ALS, TLS (Box 13)
  - S. A. Everitt to Ellen Glasgow, 1926 Oct 19; AN (Box 13)
  - S. A. Everitt to Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Dec 20; TL (Box 13)
  - S. A. Everitt to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Feb 4; TLS (Box 13)
  - Frank D. Fackenthal to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 4; Telegram (Box 14)
  - Frank D. Fackenthal to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 8; ALS (Box 14)
  - Mrs. George James Farnsworth to Ellen Glasgow, n.d.; ANS (Box 14)
  - William P. Few to Ellen Glasgow, 1936 May 8; TLS (Box 14)
  - William P. Fewto Ellen Glasgow, 1937 Apr 19; TLS (Box 14)
  - William P. Fewto Ellen Glasgow, 1938 Apr 2; TLS (Box 14)
  - John Finley to Ellen Glasgow, 1939 Apr 5; TLS w/autograph note (Box 14)
  - Dorothy Canfield Fisher to Ellen Glasgow, 1933 Jan 6; ALS (Box 14)
  - Dorothy Canfield Fisherto Ellen Glasgow, 1934 Jun 5; ALS (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freemanto Ellen Glasgow, 1933 Oct 12; TLS (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Jan 2; TLS (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 May 7; Telegram (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Dec 14; TLS (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1936 Oct 17; TLS (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1938 Jan 30; ALS (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1938 Jun 9; TLS (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1940 Feb 1; TLS w/encl. (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Apr 27; TLS (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Oct 27; TLS (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1943 Apr 3; TLS (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1944 Dec 11; TLS (Box 14)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman to Ellen Glasgow, 1945 Nov 20; TLS (Box 14)
  - Eleanor Frenchto Irita Van Doren, 1955 Mar 31; TLS (Box 14)
  - Lillie Hamilton Frenchto Ellen Glasgow, 1916 Jun 26; TLS (Box 14)
  - Lillie Hamilton French to Ellen Glasgow, 1916 Dec 30; APCS (Box 14)
  - Iona Gale to Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Apr 14; ALS (Box 14)
  - Iona Gale to Ellen Glasgow, 1928 Jul 8; ALS (Box 14)
  - Iona Galeto Ellen Glasgow, 1928 Dec 22; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ada Galsworthy to Ellen Glasgow, 1914 Jun 17; ALS (Box 14)
  - John Galsworthy to Ellen Glasgow, 1914 Jul 13; ALS (Box 14)
  - Lewis Gannett to Ellen Glasgow, 1931 Sep 23; TLS (Box 14)
  - Mary Carter Anderson Gardner to Ellen Glasgow, 1944 Mar 10; ALS (Box 14)
  - Hamlin Garland to Ellen Glasgow, 1933 Sep 17; ALS (Box 14)
  - Maxwell Geismarto Ellen Glasgow, 1944 Mar 6; TLS (Box 14)
  - P. G. Geroni to Ellen Glasgow, 1912 Jan 30; ALS (Box 14)
  - P. G. Geroni to Ellen Glasgow, 1912 May 2; ALS (Box 14)
  - Annie G. Glasgow to Joseph R. Anderson, 1881; ALS (Box 14)
  - Arthur G. Glasgow to Ellen Glasgow, 1922 Jun 9; ALS (Box 14)
  - Arthur G. Glasgow to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Oct 11; ALS (Box 14)
  - Arthur G. Glasgow to Ellen Glasgow, 1931 Dec 3; TLS w/encl. (Box 14)
  - Arthur G. Glasgow to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Dec 6; ALS w/encl. (Box 14)
  - Arthur G. Glasgow to Ellen Glasgow, 1940 Jun 25; ALS (Box 14)
  - Arthur G. Glasgow to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Apr 14; TLS (Box 14)
  - Arthur G. Glasgow to Ellen Glasgow, 1945 Apr 14; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Edwin Balmer, 1938 May 14; TLS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to John Chamberlain, 1935 Dec 2; TLS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Clifton Fadiman, 1938 Jan 23; TLS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to William P. Few, 1936 May 10; TLS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Miss Forbes, 1935 Dec 3; TLS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Lewis Gannett, 1935 Jul 25; TLS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to My Literary Executors, 1944 Feb 8; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Daniel Longwell, n.d.; TLS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Cary Glasgow McCormack, [1896 Apr 28]; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Cary Glasgow McCormack, 1896 July 23; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Cary Glasgow McCormack, 1896 Aug 2; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Cary Glasgow McCormack, 1896 Sept 9; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Cary Glasgow McCormack, [1896 Aug 1]; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Cary Glasgow McCormack, 1909 Apr 28; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Cary Glasgow McCormack, [1909] Sep 3; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Frank V. Morley, 1945 Mar 8; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Miss Patterson, 1936 Mar 4; TL (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Harry Scherman, 1937 Jan 14; TLS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mr. Sharpley (model letter), 1936 Mar; TL (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Amélie Rives Troubetzkoy, 1927 Aug 25; APC (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Amélie Rives Troubetzkoy, 1937 Jul 14; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Amélie Rives Troubetzkoy, 1937 Sep 28; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Amélie Rives Troubetzkoy, 1937 Aug 27; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Amélie Rives Troubetzkoy, 1941 Oct 6; APC (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1914 Jun 6; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, [1927 May 30]; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1927 Jul 23; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1927 Jun 26; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1927 Jul 30; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, [1927] Aug 7; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, [1927] Aug 11; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1927 Aug 16; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1927 Aug 24; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1927 Aug 31; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1927 Sep 6; ALS (Box 14)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, [1931 Dec]; ALS (Box 15)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1939 Aug 25; APCS (Box 15)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, [1945] Jul 15; APCS (Box 15)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, [1945] Jul 22; APCS (Box 15)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1945 Jul 27; APCS (Box 15)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1945 Aug; APCS (Box 15)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1945 Oct 18; TPCS w/autograph note (Box 15)
  - John Cook Wyllie to Mrs. C. C. Tutwiler, 1963 Jul 3; TL (carbon) (Box 15)
  - Ellen Glasgow to Mrs. John Y. G. Walker(draft), n.d.; Telegram (Box 15)
  - [ Ellen Glasgow] - Note on Photograph Order, n.d.; [A]N (Box 15)
  - Margaret Glasgow to Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Apr 26; TLS (Box 15)
  - Margaret Glasgow to Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Jul 14; ALS (Box 15)
  - Margaret Glasgow to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Aug 24; TLS w/autograph note and encl. (Box 15)
  - Isa Glennto Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Nov 17; TLS (Box 15)
  - Isa Glennto Ellen Glasgow, 1931 Dec 2; TLS (Box 15)
  - Isa Glennto Ellen Glasgow, 1933 May 7; TLS (Box 15)
  - Isa Glennto Ellen Glasgow, 1933 Aug 4; ALS (Box 15)
  - Armistead C. Gordon, Jr.to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Apr 15; TLS (Box 15)
  - W. E. Griffithto Ellen Glasgow, 1926 Dec 8; ALS (Box 15)
  - Francis H. Griswoldto Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Nov 17; TLS (Box 15)
  - Francis H. Griswoldto Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Dec 12; ALS (Box 15)
  - Allan T. Gwathmeyto Ellen Glasgow, 1943 Dec 21; ALS (Box 15)
  - Radclyffe Hallto Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Aug 24; ALS (Box 15)
  - Radclyffe Hallto Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Sep; ALS, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Radclyffe Hallto Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Jul-Nov; ALS, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Radclyffe Hallto Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Jun-Sep; ALS, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Radclyffe Hallto Ellen Glasgow, 1933 May 26; ALS (Box 15)
  - Radclyffe Hallto Ellen Glasgow, 1936 Mar 15; ALS (Box 15)
  - Radclyffe Hallto Ellen Glasgow, 1943 Jan 7; TLS w/autograph note and encl. (Box 15)
  - Radclyffe Hallto Ellen Glasgow, 1943 Mar 22; ALS (Box 15)
  - Nina Hamiltonto Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Dec 13; ALS (Box 15)
  - Nina Hamiltonto Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Jan 2; TLS (Box 15)
  - Nina Hamiltonto Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Jan 3; TLS (Box 15)
  - Harry Hansento Ellen Glasgow, 1943 Oct 14; TLS (Box 15)
  - Alfred Harcourt to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Nov; TLS, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Alfred Harcourt to Ellen Glasgow, 1934 Jun; TLS, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Alfred Harcourtre contract with Ellen Glasgow to publish her books, 1934 Jul 31; ANS (Box 15)
  - Alfred Harcourt to Ellen Glasgow, 1934 Aug; TLS, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Alfred Harcourt to Ellen Glasgow, 1934 Aug 13; Telegram (Box 15)
  - Alfred Harcourt to Ellen Glasgow, 1934 Aug 20; TLS (Box 15)
  - Alfred Harcourt to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Jan 29; TLS (Box 15)
  - Alfred Harcourt to Ellen Glasgow, w/encl., 1942 Feb 26; TLS w/encl. (Box 15)
  - Alfred Harcourt to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Mar 4; ALS (Box 15)
  - Alfred Harcourt and Ellen Harcourt to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 5; Telegram (Box 15)
  - Ellen Harcourt to Ellen Glasgow, 1940 Sep 11; ALS (Box 15)
  - Ellen Harcourt to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Feb 11; ALS (Box 15)
  - F. E. Hardy to Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Aug 17; ALS (Box 15)
  - Voucher and Royalty check from Harper & Brothers to Ellen Glasgow, 1916 May 1 (Box 15)
  - Leslie Hartleyto Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Aug 4; ALS (Box 15)
  - Henry Hazlittto Ellen Glasgow, 1933 Feb 15; TLS (Box 15)
  - Joseph Hergesheimerto Ellen Glasgow, 1924 Jan 24; TLS (Box 15)
  - Joseph Hergesheimer to Ellen Glasgow, 1924 May 1; ALS (Box 15)
  - DuBose Heywardto Ellen Glasgow, 1925 Dec 29; ALS (Box 15)
  - DuBose Heywardto Ellen Glasgow, 1931 Feb 10; ALS (Box 15)
  - DuBose Heywardto Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Oct 8; TLS w/autograph note (Box 15)
  - Addison Hibbardto Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Apr 26; TLS (Box 15)
  - Addison Hibbard to Ellen Glasgow with enclosed clippings and citation for honorary degree of Dr. Lit., 1930 Jun 14; TLS (Box 15)
  - Addison Hibbard to Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Dec 26; ALS (Box 15)
  - Malvina Hoffman to Ellen Glasgow, 1937 Mar 31; ALS (Box 15)
  - Malvina Hoffman to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Jun 13; ALS (Box 15)
  - Pendleton Hogan to Ellen Glasgow, 1938 Oct 17; ALS (Box 15)
  - Ward A. Holden to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Apr-Aug; ALS, 11 folders (Box 15)
  - Ward A. Holden to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Sep 11; ALS (Box 15)
  - Ward A. Holden to Ellen Glasgow, 1936 Feb 4; ALS (Box 15)
  - Receipted Bill: Hollywood Cemetery to Ellen Glasgow, 1916 Jun 1 (Box 15)
  - Hamilton Holt to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Nov; TLS, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - William Dean Howells to Ellen Glasgow, 1912 Mar 4; ALS (Box 16)
  - Marie Howland to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Aug 9; ALS (Box 16)
  - Jay B. Hubbell to Ellen Glasgow, 1931 Feb 13; TLS (Box 16)
  - Richard Hughes to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 May 8; ALS (Box 16)
  - Fannie Hurst to Ellen Glasgow, 1925 Dec 28; ALS (Box 16)
  - Peter M. Jack to Ellen Glasgow, 1943 Jan; TLS (Box 16)
  - Malcolm Johnson and Curtice Hitchcock to Frank V. Morley, 1942 Apr; TLS (Box 16)
  - Robert Underwood Johnson to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Apr 30; TLS (Box 16)
  - Robert Underwood Johnson to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Jan 8; TLS (Box 16)
  - Mary Johnston to Ellen Glasgow, 1925 Apr 8; ALS (Box 16)
  - Mary Johnston to Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Jun 15; ALS (Box 16)
  - Mary Johnston to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Sep 28; ALS (Box 16)
  - Mary Johnston to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Sep 16; ALS (Box 16)
  - Bessie Jones to Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Dec 27; ALS (Box 16)
  - Bessie Jones to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Feb 9; TL (fragment) (Box 16)
  - Bessie Jones to Ellen Glasgow, 1937 Dec 29; ALS (Box 16)
  - Bessie Jones to Ellen Glasgow, 1940 Sep-Dec; ALS, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Bessie Jones to Ellen Glasgow, 1945 Feb 27; TLS (Box 16)
  - Bessie Jones and Howard Mumford Jones to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 4; Telegram (Box 16)
  - Howard Mumford Jones to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Jul 20; TLS (Box 16)
  - Bessie Jones and Howard Mumford Jones to Ellen Glasgow, 1931 Mar 27; TLS (Box 16)
  - Howard Mumford Jones to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Jan 6; TLS (Box 16)
  - Howard Mumford Jones to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Aug 12; TLS (Box 16)
  - Blanche T. King to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Aug 29; ALS (Box 16)
  - Mrs. Alfred A. Knopf to Ellen Glasgow, 1944 May 26; TLS (Box 16)
  - Clare Leighton to Ellen Glasgow, 1936 Jan-Jun; ALS, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Clare Leighton to Ellen Glasgow, 1939 Mar 13; ALS (Box 16)
  - Clare Leighton to Ellen Glasgow, [?] Jun 20; ALS (Box 16)
  - Clare Leighton to Ellen Glasgow, 1939 Aug 31; ALS (Box 16)
  - Clare Leighton to Ellen Glasgow, [?] Sep 17; TLS (Box 16)
  - Clare Leighton to Ellen Glasgow, 1939 Nov-Dec; ALS, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Clare Leighton to Ellen Glasgow, 1940 Feb-Nov; TLS, 5 folders (Box 16)
  - Clare Leighton to Ellen Glasgow, [?] Dec 14; ALS (Box 16)
  - Literary Executors from Ellen Glasgow, 1945 Jan 6; ALS (Box 16)
  - Daniel Longwell to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Apr 22; TLS (Box 16)
  - Daniel Longwell to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Aug 25; TLS (Box 16)
  - Daniel Longwell to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Sep; TLS, 4 folders w/enclosures (Box 16)
  - Daniel Longwell to Ellen Glasgow, 1933 May 10; TLS (Box 16)
  - Daniel Longwell to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 6; Telegram (Box 16)
  - Amy Loveman to Ellen Glasgow, 1933 May 8; ALS (Box 16)
  - Amy Loveman to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 8; ALS (Box 16)
  - Elizabeth Lucas to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Aug 19; ALS (Box 16)
  - Mark Lutz to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Apr 10; TLS (Box 16)
  - John H. H. Lyon to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 6; TLS (Box 16)
  - F. Houston Martin to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Nov 5; ALS (Box 16)
  - Betsy Burke Mayo to Ellen Glasgow, [?] Sep 20; ANS (Box 16)
  - George Barr McCutchen to Ellen Glasgow, 1926 Dec 21; ALS (Box 16)
  - Jean Kenyon Mackenzie to Ellen Glasgow, 1933 May 8; ALS (Box 16)
  - Edwin Markham to John J. Newbegin, 1915 Jun 2; ALS (Box 16)
  - John P. Marquand to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 6; TLS (Box 16)
  - Julian R. Meade to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Jun 2; TLS (Box 16)
  - Julian R. Meade to Ellen Glasgow, 1936 Jun; TLS, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - H. L. Mencken to Ellen Glasgow, 1928 Oct 10; TLS (Box 16)
  - H. L. Mencken to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 Aug-Nov; TLS, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - H. L. Mencken to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Mar-Nov; TLS, 8 folders (Box 16)
  - H. L. Mencken to Ellen Glasgow, 1936 Feb 27; TLS (Box 16)
  - H. L. Mencken to Ellen Glasgow, 1938 Dec 23; TLS (Box 16)
  - H. L. Mencken to Ellen Glasgow, 1939 Jan-Dec; TLS, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - H. L. Mencken to Ellen Glasgow, 1940 Jul 24; TLS (Box 16)
  - H. L. Mencken to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Mar; TLS, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - H. L. Mencken to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Dec 26; TLS (Box 17)
  - H. L. Mencken to Sara [Haardt], n.d.; TLS (Box 17)
  - Sara Mencken to Ellen Glasgow, 1933 Oct 31; TLS (Box 17)
  - Sara Mencken to Ellen Glasgow, 1934 May 21; ALS (Box 17)
  - Edwin Mims to Ellen Glasgow, 1925 Jan 28; ALS (Box 16)
  - Edwin Mims to Ellen Glasgow, 1931 Jan-Apr; ALS, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Edwin Mims to Ellen Glasgow, 1934 Jan 1; ALS (Box 17)
  - Edwin Mims to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Jul 18; ALS (Box 17)
  - Edwin Mims to Ellen Glasgow, 1941; ALS (Box 17)
  - Edwin Mims to Ellen Glasgoww/encl., 1943 Sep 23; ALS (Box 17)
  - Edwin Mims to Ellen Glasgow, 1945 Feb 6; ALS (Box 17)
  - M. Jeannette Mitchell to Ellen Glasgow, 1921 Oct 17; ALS (Box 17)
  - Margaret Mitchell to Ellen Glasgow, 1940 Nov 11; TLS (Box 17)
  - Margaret Mitchell to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 7; Telegram (Box 17)
  - Elena Mitcoff to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Apr 16; ALS (Box 17)
  - Mary Montz to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Jan 18; ALS (Box 17)
  - Paul D. Moody to Ellen Glasgow, 1940 Feb 9; TLS (Box 17)
  - R. Walton Moore to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Sep 6; TLS (Box 17)
  - Frank V. Morley to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Feb 2; TLS (Box 17)
  - Frank V. Morley to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 4; Telegram (Box 17)
  - Frank V. Morley to Ellen Glasgow, 1944 Jan; ALS, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Frank V. Morley to Ellen Glasgow, 1944 Feb; TLS, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Frank V. Morley to Ellen Glasgow, 1944 Mar-May; ALS, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Frank V. Morley to Ellen Glasgow, 1945 Feb-Oct; TLS, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Elizabeth C. Morrow to Ellen Glasgow, 1933 Dec 18; TLS (Box 17)
  - Mrs. Vernon Munroe to Ellen Glasgow(form letter), 1933 Dec 23; ALS (Box 17)
  - Blair Niles to Ellen Glasgow, 1929 May 20; ALS (Box 17)
  - Blair Niles to Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Mar 9; TLS (Box 17)
  - Blair Niles to Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Apr 27; ALS (Box 17)
  - Blair Niles to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Oct 2; TLS (Box 17)
  - Harry Goddard Owen to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Apr-May; ALS, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Arthur W. Page to Ellen Glasgow, 1925 Apr 7; TLS w/encl. (Box 17)
  - Gabriella Page to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Aug 3; APCS (Box 17)
  - F. I. Paradise to Ellen Glasgow, 1925 Aug 2; ALS (Box 17)
  - F. I. Paradiseto Ellen Glasgoww/encl., 1925 Oct 17; ALS (Box 17)
  - Isabel Paterson to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Dec 2; TLS (Box 17)
  - Maxwell E. Perkins to Ellen Glasgow, 1937 May-Dec; TLS, 14 folders (Box 17)
  - Maxwell E. Perkins to Ellen Glasgow, 1938 Jan-Dec; TLS, 6 folders (Box 17)
  - Maxwell E. Perkins to Ellen Glasgow, 1939 Dec 27; TLS (Box 17)
  - William Lyon Phelps to Ellen Glasgow, 1933 Jun 5; ALS (Box 17)
  - William Lyon Phelps to Ellen Glasgow, 1940 Aug 27; ALS (Box 17)
  - John Cowper Powys to Ellen Glasgow, 1926 Dec 24; ALS (Box 17)
  - Arthur Hobson Quinn to Ellen Glasgow, 1936 Jun 6; ALS (Box 17)
  - Arthur Hobson Quinn to Ellen Glasgow, 1936 Jul-Nov; TLS, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Arthur Hobson Quinn to Ellen Glasgow, 1943 Sep 24; ALS w/encl. (Box 17)
  - Burton Rascoe to Ellen Glasgow, 1930 Jan 9; TLS (Box 17)
  - Burton Rascoe to Ellen Glasgow, n.d.; ALS (Box 17)
  - Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Mar 30; ALS (Box 17)
  - Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Jul 19; TLS (Box 17)
  - Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Jan 17; TLS w/encl. (Box 17)
  - Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Apr-May; TLS, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings to Ellen Glasgow, 1943 Oct 7; TLS (Box 17)
  - Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings to Ellen Glasgow, 1944 May 24; TLS (Box 17)
  - Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings to Ellen Glasgow, 1945 May, Nov; TLS, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Agnes B. Reese to Ellen Glasgow, 1937 Nov 1; ALS (Box 17)
  - Agnes B. Reese to Ellen Glasgow, 1938 May 14; ALS (Box 17)
  - Agnes B. Reese to Ellen Glasgow, 1941 Dec 27; ALS (Box 17)
  - Agnes B. Reese to Ellen Glasgow, 1924 Jan-Mar; ALS, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Agnes Repplierre Ellen Glasgow's work, to "Herald Tribune Books", [1924] Jul 22; ALS (Box 17)
  - Agnes Repplier to Ellen Glasgow, 1925 May 10; ALS (Box 17)
  - Paul R. Reynolds to Ellen Glasgow, 1916 Jul 7; TLS (Box 17)
  - David A. Robertson to Ellen Glasgow, 1935 Dec 27; TLS (Box 17)
  - David A. Robertson to Ellen Glasgow, 1938 Sep 14; TLS (Box 17)
  - Blair Rouse to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Aug 29; ALS (Box 17)
  - Millie H. Sanford to Ellen Glasgow, 1937 Sep 13; ALS (Box 18)
  - Martha P. Saxton to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Sep 15; ALS (Box 18)
  - Dorothy Scarborough to Ellen Glasgow, 1932 Dec 22; TLS (Box 18)
  - Miss Schneider from [?], 1943 Nov 7; ALS (Box 18)
  - G. C. Sellery to Ellen Glasgow, 1937 Apr; TLS, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Stuart P. Sherman to Ellen Glasgow, 1925 Apr-Sep; ALS, 5 folders (Box 18)
  - May Sinclair to Ellen Glasgow, 1924 May 22; ALS (Box 18)
  - May Sinclair to Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Aug 9; ALS (Box 18)
  - Dr. Joel Skidmore- Dental Bill to Ellen Glasgow, 1915 Nov 1 (Box 18)
  - Leonora Speyer to Ellen Glasgow, [1942] Mar 15; ALS (Box 18)
  - Leonora Speyer to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 5; Telegram (Box 18)
  - Leonora Speyer to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 Jun 9; ALS (Box 18)
  - Hunter Stagg to Ellen Glasgow, 1943 Mar 17; ALS (Box 18)
  - Hunter Stagg to Ellen Glasgow, 1944 Jan-Jun; ALS, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - George Sterling to John J. Newbegin, 1915 Jun 1; ALS (Box 18)
  - George Stevens to Daniel Longwell, 1932 Sep 24; TLS (Box 18)
  - George Stevens to Ellen Glasgow, 1942 May 5; TLS (Box 18)
  - Ruth McE. Stuart to Ellen Glasgow, 1910 Dec 8; ALS (Box 18)
  - Frank Swinnerton to Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Aug 11; ALS (Box 18)
  - Frank Swinnerton to Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Aug [13]; ALS (Box 18)
  - Frank Swinnerton to Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Sep 5; ALS (Box 18)
  - Joseph Szigeti to Ellen Glasgow, 1927 Dec 14; ALS (Box 18)